<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on www.kobinabentum.nft</title>
    <link>https://kobinabentum.nft/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on www.kobinabentum.nft</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kobinabentum.nft/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Saving Grace</title>
      <link>https://kobinabentum.nft/posts/saving-grace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kobinabentum.nft/posts/saving-grace/</guid>
      <description>Last week, we spoke about having a budget and trying to live well below that budget. One major benefit of this is that we learn to exercise restraint when it comes to to our expenses. However, there was a lot of flexibility with that tip. This week, we want to refine this concept a bit more. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in folks!
Let&amp;rsquo;s say a great misfortune came upon you and you were fired from your current work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracker Time</title>
      <link>https://kobinabentum.nft/posts/tracker-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kobinabentum.nft/posts/tracker-time/</guid>
      <description>I once spoke to a colleague about managing money and he seemed surprised about the results I was getting from my money-management practices. He complained about how he found it difficult to manage his money because the money often just vanished.
That was intriguing for me. How could your money just vanish? At least, you should know what you did with your funds. So I challenged him to track his expenditure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Personal Wealth and Development</title>
      <link>https://kobinabentum.nft/posts/personal-wealth-and-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kobinabentum.nft/posts/personal-wealth-and-development/</guid>
      <description>Everybody wants money! At least, everyone I know. Interestingly, if you are to ask them what they have done today to get them the money they want, it&amp;rsquo;ll be difficult for them to say, but I digress. From my own experience, I have found that understanding the motivations for your desires really helps you strategize to get your desires. So that&amp;rsquo;s the first thing to find out for yourself - why do you want to be wealthy?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>